{
    "id": "a0a2fbd7d6c84d348a1edca4c5dc11c7",
    "title": "Kinds of nouns exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c3fa74d3ddb546e2a24eee8d6671ab27",
            "title": "Kinds Of Nouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The book was lying on the table.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Book is a common noun",
                        "Book is a proper noun",
                        "Book is a collective noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Love begets love.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Love is a common noun",
                        "Love is a collective noun",
                        "Love is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We cannot live without water.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Water is a common noun",
                        "Water is a material noun",
                        "Water is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The jury has given its verdict.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Jury is a collective noun",
                        "Jury is a common noun",
                        "Jury is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Hindus regard Krishna as an incarnation of Lord Vishnu.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Hindus is a common noun",
                        "Hindus is a proper noun",
                        "Hindus is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Alcohol is injurious to health.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Health is a common noun",
                        "Health is an abstract noun",
                        "Health is a proper noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Smoking is a bad habit.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Habit is a common noun",
                        "Habit is a proper noun",
                        "Habit is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wild animals live in forests.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Animals is a common noun",
                        "Animals is a proper noun",
                        "Animals is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The childhood of Peter was full of misery.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Childhood is a common noun",
                        "Childhood is an abstract noun",
                        "Childhood is a proper noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "All the girls were singing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Girls is a common noun",
                        "Girls is a proper noun",
                        "Girls is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Gold is a precious metal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Gold is a proper noun",
                        "Gold is an abstract noun",
                        "Gold is a material noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rice is the staple food of South Indians.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Rice is a common noun",
                        "Rice is a material noun",
                        "Rice is an abstract noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The earth moves round the sun.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Earth is a common noun",
                        "Earth is an abstract noun",
                        "Earth is a proper noun"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}